[{"question":"What types does ECMA script supports?",
  "answers":["Undefined","Boolean","Number","All of the above"],
  "correct_answer":3},
  {"question":"What complex data type does ECMA script support?",
    "answers":["String","Object","Array","Number"],
    "correct_answer":1},
  {"question":"Does ECMA allows us to define our own data types?",
    "answers":["Yes","No"],
    "correct_answer":1},
  {"question":"When defining a variable without initializing it, what will be its type?",
    "answers":["Boolean","Number","Undefined","String"],
    "correct_answer":2},
  {"question":"What result will retrun typeof function when the parameter is null?",
    "answers":["Boolean","Object","Undefined","String"],
    "correct_answer":2},
  {"question":"What is the acronyms of the word 'Ajax'?",
    "answers":["Asynchronous JavaScript and XSD","Asynchronous Jason and XML","Asynchronous JavaScript and XML",
      "Alert JavaScript and XML"],
    "correct_answer":2},
  {"question":"Is it possible to define classes and interfaces in TypeScript?",
    "answers":["Yes","No"],
    "correct_answer":0},
  {"question":"Applications written in TypeScript based on what web language?",
    "answers":["PHP","Node.js","JS","CSS"],
    "correct_answer":2},
  {"question":"What should be done in order to code in TypeScript using PHPStorm?",
    "answers":["Access the Default Preferences setting window","Enable the TypeSciprt compiler",
      "Specify the main file we want to compile","All of the above"],
    "correct_answer":3},
  {"question":"What is the extension of a TypeScript file?",
    "answers":["js","ts","st","php"],
    "correct_answer":1},
  {"question":"Will TypeScript try to execute a code despite compiler error ?",
    "answers":["Yes","No"],
    "correct_answer":0},
  {"question":"The jQueryMobile allows us to create a unified user interface that works across most smartphones ?",
  "answers":["Yes","No"],
  "correct_answer":0},
  {"question":"Does TypeScript support the following common binary operators: << >> >>> & ?",
    "answers":["Yes","No"],
    "correct_answer":0}
]
